Now we move to the last step here is to use the token 2 register to the runner.
We need after we set the getlab runner to register with our repo that we have created earlier on the getlab website.
So we need first before we can do that, we need it will ask for the following details.
For the getlab URL, sorry, the getlab URL and it will need the access token, the access token, how I can get it from the website.
If we go to here we are on the projects, if we go to settings and CI, because it is the CI CD pipeline that we are using.
And runners as create project runner.
Let's name it for example WordPress or DevOps.
Can name it any tags that you wish.
Okay, and you also can make any description. For example, it is local branch.
And let's create it.
Okay, when we created this is the platform that we are using Linux. This is the container, for example, docker or Kubernetes.
We are using here Docker.
So the first step here at URL, you need to enter this URL and this is the token that you need to use it.
So first let's type getlab runner register to register with our repo.
And here we need to type HTTPS getlab.com, this is the getlab URL.
And then it will prompt you for the token and of course, this is the token that you have you need to copy it.
And enter a name for the runner, this is we'd be stored on the configuration dot to ml. This will be name internal with name it internal runners just as a name that we are set on the getlab website.
And executor we are dealing with shell, not here dealing with anything for the this runner will communicate via shell, so we will select the executor because we'll execute the deploy dot SS edge in a shell, so we'll use the executor as a shell here.
Okay, so the configuration here is saved.
And if you want to view runners here on the website, you can view here the local runner, it is online because we have already connected and enter the token.
And this is my IP, okay, this is my IP from Egypt, my public IP, okay, so it is connected and this is our text that we have set.
So, you know, this section is a little bit lengthy, but I hope that I have clarified all of the ideas in it. Of course, if you have any question bounties, is it it to ask me and hope to see you in the last section of the section five of the, in which I would explain the.
For an implementation of infrastructure as a goal. Thank you for your listening and see you on the next section.